{
  "data": [ {
    "id": 1,
    "name": "Angular",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is Angular?",
        "options": [
          { "id": 1, "value": "A programming language" },
          { "id": 2, "value": "A web development framework" },
          { "id": 3, "value": "A database management system" },
          { "id": 4, "value": "An operating system" }
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is the current stable version of Angular?",
        "options": [
          { "id": 1, "value": " Angular 1" },
          { "id": 2, "value": "Angular 2" },
          { "id": 3, "value": "Angular 11" },
          { "id": 4, "value": "Angular 16" }
        ],
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is TypeScript?",
        "options": [
          { "id": 1, "value": "A web development framework" },
          { "id": 2, "value": "An operating system" },
          { "id": 3, "value": "Super set of Javascript" },
          { "id": 4, "value": "A markup language" }
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is the name of the main file in an Angular application?",
        "options": [
          { "id": 1, "value": "index.js" },
          { "id": 2, "value": "main.ts" },
          { "id": 3, "value": "app.js" },
          { "id": 4, "value": " bundle.js" }
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is the command used to generate a new component in an Angular application?",
        "options": [
          { "id": 1, "value": "ng generate" },
          { "id": 2, "value": "ng create" },
          { "id": 3, "value": "ng add" },
          { "id": 4, "value": "ng update" }
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ]
  },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Java",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What is Java?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": " A programming language" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "A web browser" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "A database management system" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "An operating system" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What is the keyword used to declare a variable that cannot be changed once initialized?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "static" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "final" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "volatile" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "transient" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What is the main feature of Java that makes it platform-independent?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "Bytecode" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "Garbage collection" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "Reflection" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "Multithreading" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "What is the name of the Java Virtual Machine implementation developed by Oracle?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "JRE" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "JDK" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "JVM" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "JAR" }
          ],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is the purpose of the \"try-catch\" block in Java?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "To handle errors and exceptions" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "To define a method" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "To instantiate an object" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "To create a loop" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "Design patterns",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What is the name of the design pattern that allows for the creation of objects without exposing the creation logic?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "Abstract Factory" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "Singleton" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "Prototype" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "Builder" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What is the name of the design pattern that allows objects to be replaced with a different object that provides the same functionality?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "Adapter" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "Bridge" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "Decorator" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "Proxy" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "What is the name of the design pattern that provides a way to ensure that only one instance of a class is created?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "Singleton" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "Factory Method" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "Abstract Factory" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "Builder" }
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What is the name of the design pattern that provides a way to access elements of an object sequentially without exposing its underlying representation?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "Composite" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "Iterator" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "Proxy" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "Decorator" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is the name of the design pattern that separates the construction of a complex object from its representation, allowing for the same construction process to create different representations?",
          "options": [
            { "id": 1, "value": "Factory Method" },
            { "id": 2, "value": "Abstract Factory" },
            { "id": 3, "value": "Builder" },
            { "id": 4, "value": "Prototype" }
          ],
          "answer": 2
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
